Hi and welcome to this video! I have new Hirogato pieces, the Rainbow PU Collection. A black catsuit
and a blue catsuit and a purple bodysuit. All of them really nice colors, really shiny and I'm
trying them on you can tag along let's go here we go first one and of course I
chose the black one first because I think this is the coolest one because
it's black and it's also a bit of rainbow shine to it that's why they call
it rainbow for you of course we have the cat in front the hero goddess signature
print and I love the cat. I think it's cute. Other than that arms are really long,
legs are really long and everything feels comfortable. We have a zipper in the
back and I do have a crotch zipper. I customized that of course you can choose
without crotch zipper or you can choose with gloves and socks for example. Just
have a look at the Hirogato homepage and all the options available also for
example with the hood. Let's just admire this one for a second again. I love the
shine and I think it fits really good. So yeah really happy. I know they have it
for a while already and I didn't get it so far. I don't know why because I have
so many other HiroGato suits. Check out my other HiroGato videos here on my
channel and of course this is a classy one black pu what do you think let me
know in the comments I put my metal bed on top I think it's always always a
great option if you want to know where to get these then check out the video
I'll link in the description text or here because I made this one myself and
and a mid tutorial on how you can do it too.
Alright, but now I am going to switch into the blue one next.
It's blue, that's what I love about it.
Gotta be honest here, it is not as stretchy as the black rainbow PU fabric.
So it was a bit of a hassle to get into the gloves and the socks.
And definitely no comparison to the nylon fabrics or the lycra spandex fabrics Irogato usually uses. So if you want to do quick and easy go for the spandex collection or the black one without gloves and socks.
But if you want to look like the real full deal here, then you have to save some time to get dressed.
Here's the full look with the heels. I opted for the open one so you can see this top part here.
and yeah signature card again it is not as tight as I thought it is so it feels a bit wider but
yeah nothing for warm weather because for me at least when I struggle to get into something like
this I'll start to sweat and then it'll get even harder so I actually I use talcum powder for the
feet and the gloves to have a bit more slight slip, whatever.
whatever.
Anyway, I got one piece left, which
is this purple bodysuit
and I'm going to get out of this again and get changed.
For this one I chose the second
highest cut here in the leg so there's one cut out even higher and obviously two more which are cut
lower so to have a variety here from my last Hirogato bodysuit this is the one I chose for this
and yeah I think the color is great it's so vibrant and I can't really decide if it's a
purple or violet something between I think more violet and yeah from behind we have this string
cut here and I chose the long arms you can also add gloves again for example as I said you can
customize these you can also get the blue without the gloves and the socks so have a look at their
shop I have a discount code for Hirogato so you should use that to get some percent off I paired
with some white tights because they are always a great match and nice contrast and also I just
don't want to stand around here naked on YouTube because yeah we're on YouTube. I visited T-Rogato
and the factory last year in November or was it December when I was in Thailand in Bangkok. I have
a video for that you can check it out. It was really interesting and nice to meet the owner
so yeah I'm happy that we have this nice collaboration and that I can show you
these nice things. Also again love the cat. And yeah I think it's another great
item in addition to all the Hiroga Artisies I already own but I have to be
honest I think I prefer the spandex ones because they have so many cool patterns
for spandex fabrics and you can choose from so many also some special designs
and limited editions so again check them out and check out my other Hirogato
video I will see you in the next video I hope had fun with this one have a nice
day bye